[
    {
        "question": "####  eom geanwyrde monuc⁠ — I am a professed monk",
        "correctAnswer": "ic",
        "explanation":"'ic' is the first person singular personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hwæt sægest ####, yrþlingc?⁠ — What say you, farmer?",
        "correctAnswer": "þu|ðu",
        "explanation":"'&THORN;u' is the second person singular personal pronoun",        
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "#### hine miclum gewundode⁠ — He wounded him severely",
        "correctAnswer": "He",
        "explanation":"'He' is the third person singular masculine personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "He hire hand nam and #### sona aras⁠ — He took her hand and she arose at once",
        "correctAnswer": "Heo",
        "explanation":"'Heo' is the third person singular feminine personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "#### cildra biddaþ þe, eala lareow, þæt þu tæce us sprecan leden⁠ — We children ask you, oh teacher, that you teach us to speak Latin",
        "correctAnswer": "We",
        "explanation":"'We' is the 1st person plural personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "#### gretton hie gesybsumum wordum⁠ — They greeted them with words of peace",
        "correctAnswer": "Hie",
        "explanation":"'Hie' is the 3rd person plural personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ne ondræde ####⁠ — Fear ye not",
        "correctAnswer": "Ge",
        "explanation":"'Ge' is the second person plural personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hæbbe #### hit on handa⁠ — I have some of it in my hand",
        "correctAnswer": "Ic",
        "explanation":"'Ic' is the first person singular personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "&THORN;u, cnapa, hw&aelig;t dydest #### todaeg⁠ — You, knave, what did you do today?",
        "correctAnswer": "þu|ðu",
        "explanation":"'&THORN;u' is the second person singular personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ða #### gefor ða feng his sunu to ðam rice⁠ — When he died, his son came to the throne",
        "correctAnswer": "He",
        "explanation":"'He' is the third person singular masculine personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Hæbbe hire ðæt #### hafaþ⁠ — Let her have what she has",
        "correctAnswer": "Heo",
        "explanation":"'Heo' is the third person singular feminine personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ungelærede #### syndon & gewæmmodlice we sprecaþ⁠ — We are unlearned and we speak ungrammatically",
        "correctAnswer": "We",
        "explanation":"'We' is the 1st person plural personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "#### woldon ða men him to mete don⁠ — They wanted to make the men food for themselves",
        "correctAnswer": "Hie",
        "explanation":"'Hie' is the 3rd person plural personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Gif #### ða lufiaþ ðe eow lufiaþ⁠ — If ye love them that loves you",
        "correctAnswer": "Ge",
        "explanation":"'Ge' is the second person plural personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Gyt flæscmettum ic bruce, forðam cild #### eom⁠ — I still partake of meat, because I am a child",
        "correctAnswer": "Ic",
        "explanation":"'Ic' is the first person singular personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "#### eart seolfa geong⁠ — You yourself are young",
        "correctAnswer": "þu|ðu",
        "explanation":"'&THORN;u' is the second person singular personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "#### hit forsóc⁠ — He refused it",
        "correctAnswer": "He",
        "explanation":"'He' is the third person singular masculine personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Drihtnes ys eorðe, and eall þæt #### mid gefyld is⁠ — The Earth is the Lord's, and all that she is filled with",
        "correctAnswer": "Heo",
        "explanation":"'Heo' is the third person singular feminine personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Ac #### witun þe bilewitne wesan⁠ — But we know you are kind",
        "correctAnswer": "We",
        "explanation":"'We' is the 1st person plural personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "#### æt Tharse ðære byrg gemetton⁠ — They met one another at the city of Tarsus",
        "correctAnswer": "Hie",
        "explanation":"'Hie' is the 3rd person plural personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": []
    },
    {
        "question": "Gif #### me ut adrifaþ fram eowrum geferscype, ge etaþ wyrta eowre grene⁠ — If ye drive me away from your community you would eat your vegetables raw",
        "correctAnswer": "Ge",
        "explanation":"'Ge' is the second person plural personal pronoun",
        "commonMistakes": [
            {
                "incorrectAnswer": "þu|ðu",
                "explanation": "'ðu' is the second person singular pronoun. However, looking at the rest of the sentence you can see the plural 'eow' which indicates that 'you' here is plural"
            }
        ]
    }
]
